erecruiting.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Experience™

[Social Buttons](http://dev.linksku.com/sharepost/index.htm "Social bookmarking button WordPress Plugin") by [Linksku](http://linksku.com/ "Discover the best links on the web")

Experience, Inc. (“Experience,” “we” or “us”) is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information of users (“you” or “User”) of the Experience Network (the “Experience Network” or the “Site”). Since we collect certain types of information about our Users, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we collect, how we use it and how to correct and change it.

College and university career centers use the Experience Network to manage student, alumni and employer/recruiter data and to automate and web-enable their on-campus recruiting programs and other career center functions. In that connection, career center staff and administrators have the ability to pre-load, access and use some personal information belonging to students and alumni of their schools. Career center staff and administrators also have the ability to access and use some or all of the user submitted personal information on the Site belonging to students and alumni of their schools and employers/recruiters who recruit at their schools, including, without limitation, the ability to send them e-mails using communication tools on the Site and, in certain instances with respect to students and alumni, to publish their resumes in the school’s resume book on the Site and to apply for jobs on their behalf. School career centers and the activities and practices of their staff and administrators are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and we are not responsible for what they do with personal information about students, alumni and employers/recruiters which is available or accessible to them on or through the Site. If you have questions regarding the practices and policies of a school’s career center with respect to your personal information, we recommend that you contact them directly. We may make content or services from other web sites available to you from links located on the Site. These other web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such web site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect**

We receive and collect personally identifiable information about individual Users of our site (such as name, contact information, demographic information, academic history, etc.):

  * From college or university career centers, alumni associations, and other school organizations; and
  * From you, on a strictly voluntary basis, by specifically requesting it from you (i) when you register on the site, (ii) when you complete or edit your profile, (iii) when you use or register for certain products and services, (iv) when you respond to surveys or questionnaires, and/or (v) when you enter or sign up for promotions or contests; and
  * From you, on a strictly voluntary basis, if and when you choose to upload resumes, cover letters, writing samples and other documents to the Site which contain personal information about you.

We may also ask you for other information from time to time, which you may choose to provide or not to provide at your sole discretion, such as information regarding your personal experiences, interests and preferences, your views on career related topics and other selected issues, your opinion regarding various features of our site, the types of jobs or candidates you are interested in, etc. In certain instances, personally identifiable information with respect to Users may also be received from one or more of our other business partners.

We do not collect or store social security numbers, bank or other financial account numbers, credit or debit card numbers, or driver’s license or state-issued identification card numbers (collectively, “Excluded Personal Information”). Career center staff and administrators that pre-load personal information belonging to students and alumni of their schools are prohibited from supplying Excluded Information. Other than requesting credit card information if and when you purchase products or services online at the Site, we will never ask you for Excluded Personal Information. If you purchase products or services online at the Site using a credit card, your credit card information is processed through a third party credit card service company, which uses encryption to protect your credit card information. (See “Security” below.)

**How We Use Personally Identifiable Information Collected**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose, display or share your personal information to or with third parties without your permission.  
We use personally identifying information we collect on the Site for the following purposes:

  * To enable you to access and utilize the various tools, features and functionality of the Site, such as applying for jobs, having job postings sent to you, creating and using job search agents, uploading documents, publishing resumes to resume books, posting and editing job listings and descriptions, searching our proprietary resume data base, etc.
  * For administering sweepstakes, contests, surveys, questionnaires, polling activities and other similar events and activities that you choose to participate in, and for other purposes specifically communicated to you when we collect the information.
  * To communicate with you with regard to your use of the Site and its services or to advise you of Site changes or other events or occurrences which may affect your access to or use of the Site.
  * To provide alumni associations or career centers at universities and colleges who are members of the Experience Network with information and statistics on student, alumni or employer Users of the Site.

If you choose to publish your resume or any other document containing personal information in a resume book or to participate in the Experience Network, your personal profile information and resume will be searchable by and accessible to employers who have access to those databases. While we endeavor to restrict access to these databases to eligible employers, we cannot guarantee that other parties will not, without our consent, gain access to these databases as well. You may remove your resume from a resume book or opt out of the Experience Network at any time. However, employers and recruiters who have access to these databases, and other parties who have otherwise gained access to these databases, may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes or other personal information of Users by any of such parties while such resumes or personal information are in resume books or the Experience Network.

With your permission, we may use your e-mail address and other contact information to send you articles, profiles, industry news and other career related information, as well as to notify you of special promotions or additional products and services offered by us or our business partners and advertisers that may be of interest to you. With your permission, we may also share your personal information with our business partners and other third parties to enable them to contact you regarding special promotions, products and services they offer which may be of interest to you. You have the ability to opt-out of these types of communications at any time (see “Opt-in/Opt-out Policy” below).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide services to Experience.

From time to time, we may also disclose personally identifiable information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others’ rights or to prevent or mitigate harm. We may also disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of Experience’s business, whether such acquisition is by merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, if Experience becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Experience or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.

All Users should be aware that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their e-mail address) to others (whether in chat rooms, message boards or discussion forums, by posting jobs, responding to job postings or applying to job opportunities or otherwise), that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties, for which Experience is not responsible.

Finally, if you provide any information to parties who operate web sites that are linked to or from our Site, or if you input your information on a co-branded registration page such as that of an Experience and partner company-sponsored contest, different rules may apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by such other party. We are not responsible for any such party’s use of your personal information. We encourage you to review these sites’ privacy policies before revealing any sensitive or personal information.

**Updating Account Information**

Experience allows you to change or correct your personal information at any time. To do so, simply log in to your Experience Network account, go to your profile, and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted.

**Opt-In/Opt-Out Policy**

When you complete your profile or register on the Site, you will be presented with a series of choices regarding whether you want to receive certain types of communications from us and/or our business partners and advertisers. If you do not wish to receive any or all of such communications, you may opt-out by responding “no” or clicking the appropriate opt-out box. By opting in to receive any and or all communications, you are granting permission to allow Experience, its business partners and advertisers to send the selected communications. We reserve the right to send you communications regarding the Site and our services, or to advise you of Site changes or other events or occurrences which may affect your access to or use of the Site (such as service announcements, administrative notices and the like) without offering you the opportunity to opt out of them.

If after opting-in to the Experience Network or to receive communications from us and/or our business partners, you wish to opt-out of participation in the Experience Network or from receiving future communications, you may do so at any time. To do so, simply log in to your Experience Network account, go to your profile, and you will find options for editing your opt-in preferences.

**Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses and Aggregated User Data**

We collect IP addresses from all Users of the Site, and collect and monitor other data and information about the activities of our Users on the Site collectively. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This data is not used to track or monitor personally identifiable information of individual Users. We gather and monitor this data to analyze trends, administer the Site, identify Users when they visit the Site, track Users’ movements on the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share this information with our partners so that they too may understand our User base and Site usage patterns, but only on a collective, aggregated basis and in a manner which does not reveal any personally identifiable information about any individual User.

**Cookies**

Cookies, which are small text files recorded in a User’s hard drive, are employed by thousands of sites to enhance users’ Web viewing experience. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user’s hard drive. Cookies allow sites and advertisers to “remember” users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify Users, although they do identify a User’s computer. We use cookies for remembering User preferences and current session information. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, more consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law.

**Security**

The account containing your registration information, profile and resume is password protected, so only you (or third parties you provide your password to) can access your account. All personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited-access servers. This Site has technical, administrative and physical security measures and safeguards in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While we’re committed to placing reasonable and appropriate safeguards to protecting your information against foreseeable risks, no computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not be able to circumvent those safeguards or use your personal information for improper purposes.

As noted above, Experience does not collect or store Excluded Personal Information (as defined above). When you purchase products or services online at the Site using a credit card, your credit card information is processed through a third party service company that uses encryption to protect that information. Encryption makes it difficult for unauthorized third parties to intercept or steal your credit card information while it is being transmitted. Experience does not process or store credit card information on the Site. For information on this credit card service company’s privacy and security practices, please [click here](http://www.verisign.com/truste/index.html?sl=071202).

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We may deem it necessary or appropriate from time to time to modify this privacy policy to reflect changes in the way we collect or use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations or industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this privacy statement at any time by posting the revised policy on this Site. Information will be handled according to the privacy statement in effect at the time the information is used. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or privacy issues relating to the Site, you can contact us online at support@experience.com or mail, phone or fax us at:

Experience.com, Inc.  
Two Faneuil Hall Marketplace, 3rd fl.  
Boston, MA 02109  
Phone: 800-583-7741  
Fax: 617-305-7901  
Attn: Client Services
